本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： YYlwj0611 Smile176 leslie仙仙 黑色风车 魔法莉露姆 向往自由
校对/后期： 海之南
上世纪八十年代 汽车可以穿越时空
Back in the '80s, you had cars that could travel through time,
可以抓鬼 还能与大卫・赫索霍夫交流
cars that caught ghosts, and cars that could talk to David Hasselhoff.
大卫・赫索霍夫 出生於美国巴蒂摩尔的德国裔演员 代表作有《霹雳游侠》
所以当我哥巴里拿到驾照那一刻
So when my Brother Barry got his license...
他终于自由了
He was finally free!
不幸的是 有我妈在
Unfortunately, with my mom,
你休想自由
you're never free.
回屋里去 现在就去
Tush inside. Now.
真见鬼啊
What the hell?
你特意坐在后面等着我吗
Are you just sitting back there waiting for me?
是啊 快去
Yes. Tush!
守则七
Rule number seven...
全神贯注于路况
Total focus on the road.
不许吃 不许载人 不许听音乐
No eating, no passengers, no music.
- 啥 - 不许听音乐
- What? - No music.
守则八
Rule number eight...
门必须锁好 窗户得一直关着
Doors must be locked and windows rolled up at all times.
- 一直哦 - 疯了吧
- All times. - That's insane!
我们接着说守则九 你只能在安全区域驾驶
Which brings us to number nine-- you only drive in safe areas.
就是说
That means...
乖乖呆在绿色区域
Stay within the green zone.
你还弄了个塑料封皮的地图
You got a map with plastic overlays?
谁那么有才啊
Who does that?
我
I do.
守则十
And rule number ten,
最重要的一条
and this is the most important rule...
到达目的地记得给我打电话
Call me when you get there.
永远记得到了后给我打电话
Always call me when you get there.
为嘛我到了要给你打电话啊
Why do I have to call you when I get there?
到了就是到了 我知道我到了
I'm there. I know I'm there.
但我不知道啊 我只知道
But I don't know. For all I know,
你可能会在荒郊野外出事故
you could be stranded in the middle of nowhere,
面朝下躺在小沟沟里
lying facedown in a ditch.
洗碗去 见鬼
Do the dishes, damn it!
是小沟沟好吧
Ditches, okay?!
你不能就这么盲目同意她
You're just blindly agreeing with her
却根本不知道她在说什么
and have no idea what she's even talking about.
我知道她在说什么
I know what she's talking about.
就这些 好好学习各州首府
Right there. Learn your state capitals.
但是你的学习态度太高傲了
But you're too much of a big shot to study.
我告诉你吧 先生
Let me tell you somethin', mister.
不久就要进大学了
College is right around the corner,
你要么好好努力 要么滚蛋
and you need to shape up or ship out.
我们正在说她愚蠢的驾驶守则呢 爸爸
We're talking about her stupid driving rules, dad.
这件事上你就不能支持下我吗 就一次 求你了
Can you stick up for me here? For once? Please?
有史以来
And for the first time,
我爸真就站在了我哥这边
my father actually took my brother's side.
没门
No.
没 从未发生
No, wait. That never happened.
这个家的糟糕程度
The amount of suck
简直让人不敢相信
in this room is unreal!
我要去看电影了
I'm going to the movies.
到了给我打电话哦
Call me when you get there!
但是打破规则
But out of principle,
巴里到那儿后并没有打电话
Barry did no call when he got there
因为他知道
because he knew that out in the world,
天高皇帝远
he was beyond my mother's reach.
巴里・戈德堡
Barry Goldberg?
这儿有谁叫巴里・戈德堡吗
Is there a Barry Goldberg here?
巴里・戈德堡
Barry Goldberg?
怎么了
Um, yeah?
你需要给你妈个电话
You need to call your mother
告诉她你安全到达这儿了
and tell her you arrived here safely.
她非常担心 伙计 这样不好啊
She's very worried, dude. Not cool.
金色年代 第一季07集
那是一九八几年的十月十八号
It was october 18th, 1980-something,
我和我姐正在看
and my sister and I were watching
有生以来见过的最有意思的事
the most entertaining thing we'd ever seen...
我爸爸正试着搞定录像机
My dad trying to work the VCR.
每次结局都是这样的
Every time it ended like this.
这破玩意坏了
The damn thing's broken!
- 没坏 我来弄就好了 - 不行
- It's not broken. Just let me do it. - No!
我受够了每次摆弄很久
I'm tired of coming to you for this
到头来还得找你求助
every single time I work late.
明白吗 我得自己搞定
All right? Gotta do it myself.
授人以渔 你听说过这句名言吧
"Teach a man to fish." You ever heard that saying?
上上个生日时你就答应教我钓鱼了
You promised to teach me to fish two birthdays ago.
别激怒我啊 这可人命关天
Stop aggravating me! This is important!
费城队参加了世界职棒系列赛
The Phillies are in the world series!
下次参赛估计得等下个世纪了
It might be another century before this happens again.
爸爸 你已经倒腾了十分钟了
Dad, you've been messing with that for ten minutes.
就让亚当来呗
Just let Adam do it.
不要
No.
给我遥控器就好 给我遥控器
Just give me the remote. Give me the remote.
这儿呢 我来弄
Here. Let me do this.
真该死
The hell?
满满都是按钮 密密麻麻的
It's covered in buttons! Covered!
别管那些按钮了 用声控就好
Don't bother with the buttons. Use the voice command.
对吧 埃里卡
Right, Erica?
是的 新技术
Right. Um, it's new.
只要拿着遥控器 对着顶端说话
Just hold the remote and speak into the top.
录制世界职棒系列赛
Record world series.
没用啊
Nothing.
嘴唇靠近点儿 爸爸
Get your lips closer, dad.
哦 我懂了 就那儿啊
Oh, I see. R-right there.
录制
Record.
没用啊
Nothing!
它还不能识别你的声音 你得说你的名字
It's not identifying your voice. You gotta say your name.
我的名字是
My name is...
默里
Murray...
戈德堡
Goldberg!
好像能听懂他似的
Like it understands him.
好吧 把那场该死的比赛录下来
All right. Just record the damn game.
她在哪儿
Where is she?
那个生了我却不给我自由的女人在哪儿 哈
Where's the woman who gave me life and nothing more, huh?
哦 哦 等等 我一直在等你
Whoa, whoa, stop. I've been waiting for you,
我们需要谈谈
and we need to talk.
忙着呢 我要给老妈打电话
Busy. I gotta call mom.
不行 跟我来
Um, no. You're coming with me.
要么别理我 要么就帮帮我...
Leave me alone, or so help me god...
你干嘛要揪我的小咪咪
Why'd you have to purple my nurple?
这跟你没关系
This doesn't involve you.
当然有关系
Of course it does!
老妈一整天都要崩溃了
Mom was freaking out all day
就因为你到目的地了没给她打电话
because you didn't call her when you got there.
当她进入焦虑状态时
And when she goes into worry mode,
把我也看管得紧紧的
she tightens the clamps on me, too.
- 你几乎毁了我的整个策略 - 什么策略
- You almost blew my whole system. - What system?
无视她的所有驾驶规则
The system where I ignore all of her driving rules
并且侥幸逃脱的策略
and get away with it.
接着说
Proceed.
上周我去两个街区外的莱妮家学习
Last week, I went to study at Lainey's house two blocks away,
像往常一样 我到了就给她打电话
and as always, I called when I got there.
我说 "老妈 我到了
I said, "I'm here, mom.
我们在放威豹乐队的音乐
We're playing Def Leppard records
做基菲爆米花 想你哦"
and making jiffy pop. Miss you."
所以呢
So?
其实... 我在听威豹乐队的音乐会...
So... I was at a Def Leppard concert...
而且是在新泽西
in New Jersey.
泽西 那可是红色区域
Jersey? That's the red zone.
说对了
Damn right it is.
和莱妮学习只是个幌子
Studying with Lainey was my cover story.
找到一个好幌子
You got a good cover story,
就可以随心所欲了
and you can do anything you want.
我甚至还去过曼哈顿
I've even been to Manhattan.
那是黑色区域
The black zone.
猜猜明晚我要去哪儿
And tomorrow night, guess where I'm going.
森林啤酒聚会
Kegger in the woods.
哇 那会是年度最棒的聚会
Whoa! That's supposed to be the best party of the year.
我的幌子就是...
And my cover story...
乐队排练
Band practice.
我从八年级起就没拉过小提琴
I haven't played violin since eighth grade,
不过她并不知道
but she doesn't know that.
不是吧 我能加入你们的乐队吗
No way. Can I join your band?
我柜子里有台电子琴
I have an electric keyboard in my closet.
笨蛋 自己玩去
Get your own thing, idiot.
那会是你们的损失
Your loss.
它有七十多种节奏设置
It has over 70 rhythm settings.
有桑巴舞 波萨诺伐舞曲 还有说唱乐
Has samba, bossa nova, rap,
有摇滚一 摇滚二...
has rock 1, has rock 2...
停 根本就没这乐队 就算有
Stop! It's not a real band, and even if it was,
你的琴弹得弱爆了
you suck at keyboard.
你什么都弱爆了
You suck at everything!
不过谢谢你的帮助
But thanks for the help.
我的小伙子们回来啦
There are my boys!
网球打得怎么样
How was tennis?
好极了 我们
Excellent. Once again,
又一次击败了弗格森姐妹
the lad and I trounced the Ferguson sisters.
我太爱你们啦
Well, I 40-love you both.
别这样
Please don't.
好吧 就座吧 你们赢得了一顿胜利晚餐
Well, come sit. You've earned yourselves a victory dinner.
我只能待几分钟
I can only stay a few minutes.
我跟那对姐妹中的一个有约
I got a date with one of the sisters.
是哪个来着
Which one again?
- 米里亚姆 - 是性感的那个 对吗
- Miriam. - She's the sexy one, right?
我不知道 我啥都没看出来
I don't know. I don't see what you see.
哦 老爸 你走之前 我给你买了件东西
Oh, dad, before you go, I bought you something.
生命警报器... "电视上的那种"
Life alert... "as seen on tv."
那个时候
Back in the day,
广告简单而切题
commercials were simple and to the point,
尤其是这个经典的...
especially this classic...
我摔倒了 我爬不起来
I've fallen, and I can't get up!
为什么没人帮帮她
Why is no one helping her?
救救她
Help her!
弗莱彻女士 我们会立刻前去救助
We're sending help immediately, Mrs. Fletcher.
太好了 他们要过去了
Oh, good, they're coming.
你在跟我开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
你为什么不直接给我买件写着
Why don't you get me a sweatshirt
"我老了"的运动衫
which says "I'm old"
然后把我送到鸭塘去喂鸭子
and send me out to the duck pond to feed the ducks?
老爸 你可是自己住
Dad, you live alone.
如果你摔倒了爬不起来怎么办
What happens if you fall and you can't get up?
我这一辈子
In my whole life,
从没绊倒 滑到或摔倒过
I've never once tripped, slipped, or fallen.
是啊 这简直是侮辱
Yeah! This is an insult!
我身体结实着呢 试试看
I'm rock solid. Go ahead.
打一下我的腰 打呀
Sock me in the kidney. Do it.
老妈 上啊 打一下外祖父
Go ahead, mom. Hit grandpa.
打呀
Do it.
老爸 我不会打你腰的
I'm not punching you in the kidney, dad.
你不想要吗 好吧 当个家庭负担
You don't want it? Fine. Be a burden on your family.
- 我会的 - 他会的
- I will. - He will.
虽然老妈自有办法达到她的目的
While my mom had her own strategy to get her way,
巴里却要用埃里卡的策略达到自己的目的
Barry was gonna use Erica's strategy to get his.
就按照我让你说的说
Just say what I told you to say.
别添枝加叶 也别做修饰渲染
Don't add anything and don't embellish.
嘿 老妈 听着
Hey, ma. Listen,
我想过了 我想说我真的很抱歉
I've been thinking, and I wanted to say how sorry I am
没在剧院给你打电话
for not calling you from the theater.
是嘛 谢谢 你这么做很成熟
Well, thank you. That's very mature of you.
谢谢你
I appreciate it.
该感谢的是你
And I appreciate you.
我知道我说的不够多
I know I don't say it enough,
不过...我爱你 美女
but... I love you, girl.
要我说
I'll tell you what.
今晚得给你多炒个好菜
You're gonna get some extra stir-fry tonight.
哦 差点忘了
Oh, I almost forgot.
明晚我能去罗杰・麦克法登家吗
Can I go to Roger Mcfadden's house tomorrow night?
我喜欢罗杰・麦克法登
I love Roger Mcfadden.
我知道你喜欢 所以我选了他...
I know you do. That's why I chose him...
教我西班牙语
to teach me Spanish.
我们有个测试
We have a quiz.
我十点就回家
I'll be home at 10:00,
回想一下 这是规定四
which is rule four, if I recall.
别担心
And don't worry.
我也会遵守其他所有的规定
I'll follow all the other rules, too.
听起来好极了(西班牙语)
That sounds muy bueno.
罗杰会告诉你什么意思的
Roger will cover that with you.
# 现在所说的就是我的独唱会 #
This speech is my recital
# 我认为它很重要 #
I think it's very vital
# 在恰好的时间 做押韵的摇滚 #
To rock a rhyme, that's right on time
# 如题所说有点棘手 我们开始吧... #
It's Tricky is the title, here we go...
# 做押韵摇滚 押韵摇滚 有点棘手 #
It's tricky to rock a rhyme, to rock a rhyme
# 时间恰好 有点棘手 #
that's right on time, it's tricky
# 有点棘手 棘手 棘手 #
It's tricky, tricky, tricky,
# 做押韵摇滚 押韵摇滚 有点棘手 #
It's tricky to rock a rhyme, to rock a rhyme
# 时间恰好 有点棘手 #
that's right on time, it's tricky
# 棘手 棘手 棘手 棘手 #
Tricky, tricky, tricky, tricky
神啊 看看谁从绿色安全区溜出来了
My god. Look who made it out of the green zone.
全托你的福
All thanks to you.
现在给我说电话在哪儿 我们马上就可以出发了
Now point me to the phone and we're good to go.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
要给妈妈打电话
Gotta call mom,
告诉她我平安到达罗杰・麦克法登家
tell her I arrived safely at "Roger Mcfadden's house.
这儿没电话
There's no phone here.
是森林里的啤酒会 森林明白不
It's the kegger in the woods. The woods?
那...附近总该有个房子吧
Well... There's gotta be a house here somewhere.
比如 伐木工人的营地 骑警驻地
I mean, a lumberjack's camp. A ranger's station.
秘密军事基地
A secret army base.
你觉得我们能在多深的森林里呀
How deep in the woods do you think we are?
我不知道 这儿是橙色危险区
I don't know. This is the orange zone.
- 我从没来过这么远 - 冷静点
- I've never gone this far. - Calm down.
你跟罗杰・麦克法登说过这一切了 对吧
You told Roger Mcfadden all about this, right?
没 罗杰和家人去海滩了
No. Roger went down the shore with his family.
你得让他掩护你
You need him to cover for you
万一妈妈给他家打电话的话
in case mom calls his house.
你以为"托词"是什么意思
What do you think "cover story" means?
意思是有人替你掩护
It means someone to cover for you!
你还想要其他人牵扯进来
You wanted other people involved?
对我来说太复杂了
This is too complicated for me!
你就应该让我直接加入你的乐队
You should have just let me join your band!
笨蛋 你会让咱俩都玩完的
Dumbass, you're gonna ruin this for the both of us!
赶紧开车去找个电话
Get in your car and drive to a phone now.
给我妈打电话 给我妈打电话
Gotta call my mom, gotta call mom.
哦 不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no.
可恶
Damn it!
我得给我妈打电话
I gotta call my mom!
埃里卡 帮帮我
Erica! Help me!
我们去那边吧
Let's go over there.
该死
Damn it.
为什么
Why?!
我得给我妈打电话 我得给我妈打电话
I gotta call my mom! I gotta call my mom!
我得给我妈打电话
I gotta call my mom!
我回家了
I'm home!
在没有电子邮件 短信 推特之前
Back before e-mails, texts, and tweets,
你能过一整天 听不到剧透
you could go a whole day without spoilers
或者不知道比赛的比分
or knowing the score of a game,
现在我爸爸终于要去观看
and now my dad was finally gonna get to watch
他这辈子最重要的一场费城队的比赛了
the most important Phillies game of his lifetime.
好了
All right.
霍华德・柯塞尔 给我点甜头吧
Howard Cosell, give me the sweet stuff.
默里 关上电视
Murray, turn that tv off!
也许没有
Or not.
哦 额滴神
Oh, god.
巴里还没打电话 他已经出去快一个小时了
Barry hasn't called. He's been gone almost an hour.
我给罗杰・麦克法登家打了电话
I called Roger Mcfadden's house.
没人接
No one's answering.
- 你打了几次 - 八次
- How many times have you called? - Eight.
等你打了十五次再说
When you hit 15, then we'll talk.
意思是你就准备坐在这儿看棒球比赛
So you're just gonna sit here and watch a baseball game
而咱们的儿子此时可能正趴在
when our son might be laying facedown
某条小沟沟里
in a ditch somewhere.
也许是 但也许不是
Might be. But might not be.
我们现在唯一能确定的是
The only thing we know for sure
我看的是世界职棒些列赛
is I'm watching the world series.
你晚上怎么能睡得着
How do you sleep at night?
另一层意思 你晚上睡得怎么样
没有白天睡得好 不过也不差
Not as good as I do during the day, but not bad.
放轻松 孩子不会有事的
Relax. Kid's gonna be fine.
不过他真有事
But he wasn't.
没问题 我能搞定
It's okay. I can fix this.
好 太好了
Okay. All right.
不
No!
妈妈
Mom!
我在罗杰家
I'm at Roger's house!
我平安到达了
I got here safely!
我爱...
I love...
当巴里整晚过得无比悲摧还马不停蹄时
While Barry's night was off and running,
我外祖父正要歇下来
my grandfather's was just winding down.
那个 我很想留你在这过夜 不过...
Yeah, I'd love for you to stay the night, but, uh...
我才发现明天早上有个早会
Turns out I got a meeting first thing in the morning.
哦 我以为你十年前就退休了呢
Well, I thought you retired ten years ago.
没错 但是我还在做一些兼职的咨询工作
Yeah, well, I still do part-time consulting
偶尔还...
and the occasional...
你需要打车钱吗
Do you need money for a cab?
这是什么
What's this?
这不就是广告里出现的那东西
This is one of those things from the commercial.
你不会也戴这玩意儿吧
Well, you don't wear one of these?
不 不 这只是个恶作剧礼物
No, no. This is just, uh, it's a gag gift
是拳击俱乐部里的某个家伙送的
from some of the guys down at the boxing club, and...
逗吧
Hilarious.
今晚过得很有意思 我会打给你的
Well, this has been fun. I'll call you.
额 不要
Uh... No.
我打给你 让我来打
I'll call you. I... I do the calling.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
他妈的
Son of a bitch!
是的 我打电话是想问我儿子
Yes, I'm calling to see if my son
是否被送进了你们的急救室
might have been brought into your emergency room
今晚早些时候
earlier tonight.
呃 他身高一米七二 黑头发 白皮肤
Uh, he is 5'8", dark hair, fair skin,
一双漂亮的棕眼睛
beautiful brown eyes.
哦 他会是你见过的最可爱的小男孩儿
Oh, he was just the sweetest little baby you've ever seen.
什么 没有吗
What? No.
好的 谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
投的什么球这是 真烂
What is that pitch?! That's garbage!
我恨你  迪奇・ 诺尔斯
I hate you, Dickie Noles!
好了 他不在急诊室
Okay. He's not in the emergency room
不在警察局
or the police station
不在溜冰场 不在棒球练习场
or the roller rink or the batting cages
也不在绿色安全区域内四家冰激凌店
or any of the four ice cream shops
的任何一家 我真是个失败的母亲
in the green zone, and I have failed as a mother.
你其他事做的还不错
You're good at other things.
巴里
Barry!
不 是 是我 亲爱的
No, it's... it's just me, darling.
- 你的电话一直占线 而我 - 现在没空
- Your line's been busy for quite a while now, and I... - Can't talk now!
该死
Damn it!
我受不了啦 出去找回我们的孩子 默里
I can't take it anymore. Go out and find our baby, Murray.
求你了 如果我出去 我就会知道比赛结果
Please! If I go out, I'll find out what happened in the game!
别管棒球了 你是不是有病啊
Enough with the baseball. What is wrong with you?
你怎么能不着急呢 他在外面哪
Why aren't you worried? He's out there.
可能伤着冻着或者饿着
He could be injured, or cold or hungry.
万一他内急怎么办 他不用公共厕所的
What if he has to make? He doesn't use public bathrooms!
贝弗 冷静点 好吗
Bevy, calm down, okay?
每次咱家小孩出门
Every time our kids leave the house,
你都会以为他们死了 直到事实证明并没有
you assume that they're dead until they prove otherwise.
要知道他们是聪明的有责任心的孩子
Know that they're smart, responsible kids.
要相信他们还活着
Assume that they're alive.
这是你说过的最蠢的话
That's the stupidest thing you've ever said!
待会儿见
I'll see you in a bit.
巴里
Barry?
不 不是巴里 是我 让亚当接电话
No, it's not Barry. It's me. Put Adam on the phone.
亚当 过来 接你外祖父电话
Adam, get in here, talk to your grandfather
不然他会一直打
so he'll stop tying up the line!
快点
Make it quick.
喂 波普斯
Yeah, pops?
当外祖父在寻求帮助时
While pops was looking for a little help,
我爸正在找巴里
my dad was out looking for Barry,
他也越来越担心
and he was growing increasingly worried
他会知道比赛结果
that he'd find out what happened in the game.
对费城球迷来说 这真是一个激动人心的夜晚啊
Quite an emotional night for Phillies fans...
要是我爸不快点找到巴里
If my dad didn't find Barry soon,
我哥就惨了
my brother was gonna pay.
打扰一下 警官
Excuse me, officer.
你有看到一个高中生在这附近开车吗
Did you see a high school kid driving around here?
头发卷卷 呆头呆脑的那个
Curly hair, kind of lumpy?
没有 但是森林里有个派对
No, but there's a party in the woods
- 在阿尔弗索普公园旁边 - 好的
- down by Alverthorpe Park. - Okay.
嘿 费城队 那个...
Hey, Phillies! Man, how about...
不不不
No, no, no!
我只是想看世界职业棒球大赛
I just wanna watch the world series!
我要杀了那个兔崽子
I'm gonna kill that kid!
波普斯 波普斯
Pops? Pops!
在这儿呢
Over here!
咋整的
What happened?
我摔了一跤...
I have fallen...
然后...起不来了
And I... Cannot get up.
就这样
There you go.
慢点 继续拖
Easy. Little more.
把浴袍往下拉点行不
Pull your robe down.
这是和服耶
It's a kimono.
那就把和服往下拉
Pull your kimono down.
他这么设计就是要炫
It's designed to be showy.
好吧 的确很炫
Well, it's working.
你别往下看就行了
Just don't look down!
我看到啥了 跟个知更鸟窝似的
What did I just see? It was like a robin's nest!
那是你角度不好
It's an unflattering angle.
那里怎么了
What's going on down there?
别看了 快把我拖到沙发那儿
Stop looking down and get me to the couch already!
哦 好吧
Oh! Okay.
你还好吗
You good?
恩 还好 我...现在没事了
Yeah, okay. I'm...I'm good now.
幸亏你来了 孩子
Thanks for dropping by, kid.
你真的没事吗
Are you sure you're good?
当然啦 这还用问
Of course. Like you even need to ask.
只是我好像记得你说过你从来没摔倒过
It's just that you said that you never fell before.
我把腰扭了 谁都可能碰到这事
I threw my back out. It could happen to anyone.
你打算拿这个怎么办
So what do you wanna do with this?
扔掉它
Chuck it!
我懂了 这玩意儿或许是有点丢人
I get it. This thing might be embarrassing,
但是...比你穿着浴袍摔倒好多了
but... no more embarrassing than that robe.
那是我那晚第二次
For the second time that night,
看到我外祖父 我从未见过的一面
I saw a part of my grandfather I'd never seen before...
那一面其实很脆弱
The part that was actually vulnerable.
停车 拜托停车
Stop! Stop! Please!
停车 停...
Stop! Sto--uhh!
停车 停车
Stop! Stop!
我只是想借用一下你的无线电告诉我妈
I need your C.B. Radio to call my mom
让她知道我很安全
so she knows I'm safe!
不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no!
我爸爸在整个镇里转了近一个小时
My dad had spent the last hour driving all over town.
就在他开始觉得
Just as he was starting to think
我妈的疯狂也许不是无稽之谈时
my mom's craziness may not have been so crazy,
他看到了一件眼熟的外套...
he spotted a familiar jacket...
哦 嗨
Oh. Hi.
和一个眼熟的蠢货
And a familiar jackass.
你就不能在沟里坐着吗
You couldn't have been sitting up in a ditch?
或者在沟里舒舒服服地躺着
Or reclining comfortably in a ditch?
你非得趴地上啊 和她说的一模一样
No, you had to be facedown, exactly like she said!
亏我还跟你妈说可以相信你
And to think I told your mom you could be trusted,
虽然主要因为我想看比赛
mostly 'cause I wanted to watch the game.
但是你知道吗 我其实有一点想
But you know what? A small part of me
嘿 他也不至于蠢得不可救药啊
actually thought, "hey, he's not a complete moron."
发生这种事 一小部分原因是我蠢得不可救药
Only some of this happened 'cause I'm a complete moron.
但主要是因为老妈制定的愚蠢的规则
The rest is 'cause of mom's stupid rules.
嘿 她制定规则还不是为了保护你
Hey, her rules are there to protect you.
我看到你的外套在马路中间 差点没把我吓死
I almost died when I saw your jacket in the road.
你也担心我吗
You worry about me, too?
拜托 别逼我说出这种话
Oh, don't put words in my mouth.
我当然担心你
Of course I do.
今晚的事 决不能让你妈知道
Your mom can't know anything about this.
啥 你要跟她撒谎吗
What? You're gonna lie to mom?
那必须的 她要是知道了
Absolutely! She finds out about this,
在你四十岁之前 你休想走出
you're not gonna be allowed to leave the house
家门一步 到那时我这辈子也完了
until you're 40, and then my life is ruined, too!
太棒了 那我就脱身了
Nice! I'm off the hook, then.
但是 你被秘密禁足了
You are so grounded. Secretly, though.
接下来三个月
You will choose to stay in every weekend
每个周末你都得待在家里 直到我大发慈悲
for the next three months, and for the love of god,
还你自由之后
when I do let you back out in the world,
你到了目的地得给我打电话
you will call me when you get there.
我会的 我保证
I will. I promise.
我替我朋友扔的
I was throwing that for a friend.
还有告诉你那个白痴姐姐 她也被秘密禁足了
And tell your stupid sister that she's secretly grounded, too.
老爸你真是太好了
Thanks for being so cool about this.
我以为费城队输了之后
I thought you'd be in the worst mood
你的心情肯定糟糕透顶
after the Phillies lost.
滚出去
Get out.
躺下来
Lie down.
我要从你身上碾过去
I'm gonna run you over.
所以我哥哥其实用三个月的自由生活
And so my brother crammed three months of partying
换来了一个疯狂的晚上
into one epic night of awesome.
至于波普斯
As for pops,
他也开始意识到
he was starting to realize it wasn't so bad
放弃一丢丢自由 换来家人的安心
to give up a piece of his freedom
也不是件坏事
for his family's peace of mind.
还是很帅
Still got it.
当时他在等拖车
So he's waiting for the tow truck,
按照守则三 他乖乖待在车里
he stays in the car, rule number three...
最终让我妈放心的
Ultimately it wasn't my mom's elaborate rules
不是她煞费苦心制定的规则
that put her at ease...
还有
And listen to this.
他现在正在罗杰・麦克法登家学习呢
He's over at Roger Mcfadden's studying right now...
而是我爸精心编排的谎言
It was my dad's elaborate lies.
他真是个乖孩子
He is such a great kid.
知道那是他们最后一晚的自由生活之后
Knowing it was their last night of freedom,
巴里和埃里卡珍惜每分每秒
Barry and Erica made every moment count...
他们的确很开心
And it was glorious...
直到五分钟后警察突袭了那个地方
Until the cops raided the place five minutes later.
今天晚上会放新版"霹雳游侠"
That's a new "Knight Rider" on tonight.
由片头出现过的的大卫・赫索霍夫主演
介意我录下来吗
Mind if I tape it?
当然不介意 其实
No! Um, as a matter of fact,
你可以试试这个新的声控功能
why don't you use, uh, the new voice command?
- 真的吗 - 当然 告诉它你的名字
- For real? - Yeah, for real. Tell it your name.
你好 我是巴里・戈德堡
Hi. I'm Barry Goldberg.
然后告诉它你要做什么
Now, uh, tell it to do something.
遥控器 转到"霹雳游侠"
Remote, turn to "Knight Rider."
太棒了
That's pretty cool.
等等 真的可以 让我试试
Wait a minute. Did it? Give it to me a second here.
回到"胡克警探"
Uh... Go back to "T.J. Hooker."
不是 错了
No, wrong way!
"胡克警探" 让它转到"胡克警探"
"T.J. Hooker"! Tell it to go back to "T.J. Hooker."
不 你自己说吧
No, you tell it.
好吧 遥控器 我是默里...戈德堡
All right, remote, this is Murray... Goldberg.
请转回"胡克警探"
Please go back to "T.J. Hooker."
不是
No!
错了
Wrong way!
你知道威廉・夏特纳主演的"胡克警探"
You know "T.J. Hooker," with William Shatner.
威廉・夏特纳 一名犹太裔的加拿大籍演员
他又陷进去了
And he fell for it again.
胡克 警探
Hooker! T.J.!
亲爱的默里老爸 抱歉总是浪费你看电视的时间
我命令你给我走开
I want you to get away from there.
挡住我了 真讨厌
I can't see, and it's very annoying.
讨厌吗
Is it annoying?
- 给我 - 哦 不
- Give me that. - Whoa. No.
把摄像机给我 我要砸了它
I want that camera. I'm gonna take it and break it!